Guide to The Boys' Club of New York Records 1876-2002 MS 3000
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI: Benefit Events and Fundraising
  - Subseries VI.1: Benefit Events
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1971, 1973 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 2)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1974 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1975 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1976 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1977 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 6)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1978 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 7)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1979 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 8)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1980 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 9)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1981 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 10)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1982 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 11)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1983 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 12)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1984 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 13)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1985 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 14)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1986 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 15)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1987 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 16)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1988 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 17)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1989 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 18)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fall Dance, invitations (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1996-1998 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 2000-2003 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 6)
    - Fall Dance, program, 1991, 2002 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 7)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1973 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 8)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1974 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 9)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence (Offsite-box 60, Folder 1)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1976 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1977 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1978 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
    - Spring Dance, correspondence, 1979 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 5)
    - Spring/Fall Dances, committees, 1987-2002 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 6)
    - Spring and Fall Dances, Information Package, 1980's (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1946, 1959 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 2)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 4)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 5)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 7)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1971 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 9)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 10)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1076-1977 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 11)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 1)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 2)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 3)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 4)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 5)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 6)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 7)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 8)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1994 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 9)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1995 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 10)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 11)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 12)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 1)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 2)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 2004-2005 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 3)
    - Spring Dance, invitations, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 4)
    - Spring Dance, programs, 1957, 1985 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 5)
    - Spring Dance, programs, 2003 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 6)
    - Theater Benefit, "Follies," correspondence, 1971 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 7)
    - Movie benefit, "The Godfather," correspondence, 1972 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 8-9)
    - Movie benefit, "Day of the Jackal," correspondence (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1)
    - Movie benefit, "Great Gatsby," correspondence, 1974 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 2)
    - Movie benefit, "Jaws," correspondence, 1975 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 3)
    - Movie benefit, "Midway," correspondence, 1976 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 4)
    - Movie benefit, "Jaws 2," correspondence (Offsite-box 64, Folder 5)
    - Movie benefit, "Moonraker," correspondence, 1979 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 6)
    - Movie benefit, "A View to Kill," correspondence, 1985 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 7)
    - Movie benefit, "Legal Eagles," correspondence, 1986 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 8)
    - Movie benefit, "The Living Daylights," correspondence, 1987 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 1)
    - Movie benefit, accounts receivable, 1990 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 2)
    - Movie benefit, invitations, 1970's (Offsite-box 65, Folder 3)
    - Movie benefit, invitations, 1980's (Offsite-box 65, Folder 4)
    - Movie benefit, invitations, 1995-2002 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 5)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1966 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 6)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1967 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 7)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1969 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 8)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 9)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1989 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1990 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 3-4)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1991 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 5-6)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1992 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1993 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 3)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1994 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 4-5)
    - Fashion show, correspondence and accounts, 1995 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 6)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1966 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 1)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1967 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 2)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 3)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 4)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1993-1995 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 5)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 6)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 2004-2005 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 7)
    - Fashion show, invitations, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 8)
    - Fashion show, programs, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 9)
    - Invitations, other events, 1966-2000 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 10-12)
    - Event committees, 1986-2002 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 1-4)
    - Event program accounts, 1966-1973 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 5)
    - Golf benefits, promotional packets, 1950's (Offsite-box 69, Folder 6)
      Includes photographs
    - Golf benefits, programs, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 7)
    - Golf benefits, programs, 1956, 1958 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 8)
      1956 program includes article on first woman golf professional (Bessie Fenn) in charge of a club in the U.S.
  - Subseries VI. 2: Benefit Events: Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner (includes photographs)
    - 1st Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1976 December 1 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1977 November 2 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 2-3)
    - 3rd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1978 November 1 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 4)
    - 4th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1979 October 1 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 6)
    - 5th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1980 October 29 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 8)
    - 6th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1981 October 28 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 9-10)
    - 7th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1982 October 27 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - 8th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1983 October 26 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 4-5)
    - 9th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1984 October 24 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 6-7)
    - 10th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1985 October 23 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 8-10)
    - 11th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1986 October 29 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - 12th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1987 October 28 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 4-6)
    - 13th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1988 October 26 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 7-8)
    - 13th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner (Offsite-box 72, Folder unknown container)
    - 13th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1988 October 26 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - 14th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1989 October 25 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 3-4)
    - 15th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1990 October 24 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 5-7)
    - 16th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1991 October 23 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 8-11)
    - 16th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1991 October 23 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 1-5)
    - 17th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1992 October 21 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 6-14)
    - 17th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1993 November 3 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 15-18)
    - 18th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1993 November 3 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 1-4)
    - 19th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1994 November 2 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 5-13)
    - 20th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1995 November 1 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 14-16)
    - 20th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1995 November 1 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 1-3)
    - 21st Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1996 October 30 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 4-10)
    - 22nd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1997 November 1 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 11-13)
    - 23rd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1998 November 4 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 14-15)
    - 24th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 1999 November 3 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 1-6)
    - 25th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2000 November 1 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 7-12)
    - 26th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2001 November 7 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 13-17)
    - 27th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2002 November 6 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 18)
    - 28th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2003 (Offsite-box 77, Folder unknown container)
    - 28th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2003 November 5 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 1)
    - 29th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2004 November 3 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 2)
    - 30th Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2005 November 2 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 3)
    - 31st Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2006 November 1 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 4)
    - 31st Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2006 (Oversize Medium, Folder BCNY OS 4)
      Mounted group photo of BCNY Board of Trustees signed by Hall of Fame inductees
    - 32nd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2007 October 30 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 5)
    - 32nd Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, 2007 October 30 (Oversize Medium, Folder BCNY OS 4)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Offsite-box 78, Folder 6-9)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, Inductee photographs, undated (Offsite-box 78, Folder 10)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, programs, 1977, 1980, 1982 (Offsite-box 78, Folder unknown container)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, programs, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 79, Folder unknown container)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner, programs, 1994-2001, 2003, 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 80, Folder unknown container)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- newsletters, invitations, and other ephemera, 1984-1994 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 1)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- newsletters, invitations, and other ephemera, 1995-1998 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 2)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- newsletters, invitations, and other ephemera, 1999-2002 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 3)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- newsletters, invitations, and other ephemera, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 4)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- newsletters, invitations, and other ephemera, 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 5)
    - Annual All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner -- news clippings, 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VI.3: Fundraising
    - Christmas solicitations, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 1)
    - Christmas solicitations, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 2)
    - Christmas solicitations, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 3)
    - Fundraising scrapbook, 1940's (Offsite-box 82, Folder 4)
    - History of gifts to endowment funds, 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 82, Folder 5)
    - Donors: William Simpson (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2032), 1956-1997 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 6-7)
    - Donors: Minot Milliken (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2032), 1947-1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - Donors: William Wallach (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2032), 1980's - 1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 3)
    - Harriman Memory Gifts, 1978 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 4)
    - Capital Campaigns(RESTRICTED UNTIL 2034), 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 5-6)
- Series VII: Photographs
  The many photographs in this collection provide a rich visual record of the activities and people associated with BCNY. Photographs span the period from the 1890's to 2000's. Although most photographs are undated, it appears that the 1940's and 1950's are especially well documented.
  Photographs are generally arranged by subject, including: neighborhood scenes; clubhouse buildings; sports (including team shots as well as game and action shots); recreational activities such as art, photography, glee club and many others; camp photographs; program activities (primarily educational); theatrical productions; pictures and portraits of officers, alumni and boys; and photographs of various fund-raising events (note that photographs of the All-Star Annual Hall of Fame event are housed separately in Series VI, Benefit events).
  In some cases, photographs by identified photographers are arranged by the name of the photographer. There are many photographs by Sam Reiss (1910-1975), better known for his photography of the labor movement in New York City; other photographers include Paul Parker, Heini Mayr, and Dick Meek. The majority of the photographs, however, are by unidentified photographers.
  Oversize photographs are listed at the end of the Series and include photographs from most or all of the categories listed above. The series also includes photo albums and photographic slides of various subjects (identified in the box and folder list) as well as negatives (largely unidentified). The same subject may appear in different formats (for example, camp photos will be found in loose photographs, photo albums, oversize photographs, and photographic slides), so in order to locate all the relevant visual material, researchers should search or browse the entire box and folder list for Series VII.
  Photographs that were exhibited at BCNY have been unframed and are housed together as "Display photos" (Box 115, Folders 3-8).
  Note that some photographs have numbers on the back preceded by "BD", "CP", or "HP"; captions for these photographs will be found in Box 115.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Photographic negatives from Series VII are digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Early photographs, circa 1890's - 1940's (Offsite-box 84, Folder 1-2)
  - Neighborhood scenes, undated (Offsite-box 84, Folder 3-4)
  - Buildings: Tompkins Square (Offsite-box 84, Folder 5)
  - Buildings: Jefferson Park and Central Park (Offsite-box 84, Folder 6)
  - Buildings: Pitt Street, 1959, undated (Offsite-box 84, Folder 7)
  - Buildings: Pitt Street expansion (Offsite-box 84, Folder 8)
  - Buildings: Dedications, Elbridge T. Gerry, Jr. Clubhouse and Milliken Building, 1986, 2007 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 9)
  - Sports: Basketball (team shots) (Offsite-box 85, Folder 1-2)
  - Sports: Basketball (Offsite-box 85, Folder 3)
  - Sports: Swimming (Offsite-box 85, Folder 4-5)
  - Sports: Wrestling and boxing champs, 1940's - 1950's (Offsite-box 85, Folder 6)
  - Sports: Wrestling, track and other sports; physical fitness (Offsite-box 86, Folder 1)
  - Sports: tennis, 1954 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 2)
  - Sports program (Offsite-box 86, Folder 3)
  - Sports: boxing (Offsite-box 86, Folder 4-6)
  - Sports: boxing (identified photographers) (Offsite-box 86, Folder 7)
  - Sports: boxing, London matches, 1950's (Offsite-box 87, Folder 1)
  - Sports: boxing, 2013 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 2)
  - Games room/recreation (includes break dancing) (Offsite-box 87, Folder 3-4)
  - Crafts (Offsite-box 87, Folder 5-6)
  - Arts and crafts (Offsite-box 87, Folder 7)
  - Art room/art shows (Offsite-box 88, Folder 1)
  - Photography club and journal staff (Offsite-box 88, Folder 2)
  - Social activities/recreation (Offsite-box 88, Folder 3)
  - Glee club (Offsite-box 88, Folder 4)
  - Band (Offsite-box 88, Folder 5)
  - Roof activities (Offsite-box 88, Folder 6)
  - Pet shows (Offsite-box 88, Folder 7)
  - Christmas parties (Offsite-box 88, Folder 8)
  - Outings and excursions (Offsite-box 89, Folder 1)
  - Little Sister shows (Offsite-box 89, Folder 2-4)
  - Father and Son buffets; awards nights (Offsite-box 89, Folder 4)
  - Camp Photographs (Offsite-box 89, Folder 5-6)
  - Camp Carey (Offsite-box 89, Folder 7-8)
  - Camp Carey: Group photos, 1930's - 1960's (Offsite-box 90, Folder 1)
  - Camp Carey: Groups of boys (Offsite-box 90, Folder 2)
  - Camp Carey: Portraits of boys (Offsite-box 90, Folder 3)
  - Camp Carey: Programs (Offsite-box 90, Folder 4)
  - Camp Carey: Mess hall (Offsite-box 90, Folder 6)
  - Camp Carey: Infirmary (Offsite-box 90, Folder 7)
  - Camp Carey: Sound Beach (Offsite-box 90, Folder 8)
  - Camp Carey: Lake (Offsite-box 90, Folder 9)
  - Camp Carey: Nature (Offsite-box 90, Folder 10)
  - Camp Carey: Landscapes (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
  - Camp Carey: Hikes and Campfires (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
  - Camp Carey: Athletics (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
  - Camp Carey: Playground (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
  - Camp Carey: Winter camping (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5-6)
  - Camp Carey: Alumni weekend (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
  - Camp Carey: Visitors (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
  - Camp Carey: photographs by Bruce Davidson, 1959, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
  - Camp Carey: snapshots (black and white) (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
  - Camp Carey: report/scrapbook, 1938 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
  - Camp Harriman: photo album (Offsite-box 91, Folder 11-13)
  - Camp Harriman (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1)
  - Camp Harriman: scrapbook (Offsite-box 92, Folder 2)
  - Camp Tabor (Offsite-box 92, Folder 3)
  - Camp Cromwell: dedication (Offsite-box 92, Folder 4)
  - Camp Cromwell, 1990-1997 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 5-7)
  - Camp Cromwell: Education program (Offsite-box 92, Folder 8)
  - Camp Cromwell: negatives (Offsite-box 92, Folder 9)
  - Programs: classroom activities (Offsite-box 92, Folder 10)
  - Programs: academic assistance and library (Offsite-box 92, Folder 11)
  - Programs: education and nature (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1)
  - Programs: Youth Development and employment (Offsite-box 93, Folder 2)
  - Programs: Dental clinic/health (Offsite-box 93, Folder 3)
  - Programs: International travel (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
  - Photo albums: clubhouse activities and excursions, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
  - Photo albums: clubhouse activities and excursions, 1990's (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6-7)
  - Photo albums: Camp Harriman, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 1)
  - Photo albums: Camp Photos, 1990's (Offsite-box 94, Folder 2)
  - Photo albums: Harriman Clubhouse, 1990's (Offsite-box 94, Folder 3-4)
  - Photo albums: Jefferson Park Clubhouse, undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 5)
  - Photo albums: Harriman Clubhouse, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 2)
  - Photo albums: Milliken Clubhouse, undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 6)
  - Photo albums: Milliken Clubhouse Leadership Conference, 1996 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 7)
  - Photo albums: Education Program (Offsite-box 94, Folder 8)
  - Photo albums: Milliken Clubhouse, undated (Offsite-box 95, Folder 1)
  - Photo albums: Camp Cromwell, clubhouse activities, 1990's -2000 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 3)
  - Photo albums: Nancy Phelan photographs (Camp Cromwell, programs, activities), 1980's - 2000's (Offsite-box 95, Folder 4-6)
  - Photo albums: "Boys Club in Action" (3 volumes), 1990's (Offsite-box 96)
  - Photo albums: Music camp, circa 1960's (Offsite-box 96)
  - Photo albums: Camp Crafts, 1968 (Offsite-box 96)
  - Theatrical productions: "Bye Bye Birdie", 1971 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 1)
  - Theatrical productions: Brigadoon (Offsite-box 97, Folder 2)
  - Theatrical productions: "Damn Yankees", 1958 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 3)
  - Theatrical productions: "Encore, Encore", 1990 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 4)
  - Theatrical productions: "Finian's Rainbow", 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 5)
  - Theatrical productions: "A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 6)
  - Theatrical productions: "Godspell", 1991 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 6A)
  - Theatrical productions: "Happy Fella" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 7)
  - Theatrical productions: "Kismet" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 8)
  - Theatrical productions: "Kiss Me Kate" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 9)
  - Theatrical productions: "Mame", 1970 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 10)
  - Theatrical productions: "Man of La Mancha" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 11)
  - Theatrical productions: "Man Who Came to Dinner" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 12)
  - Theatrical productions: "My Fair Lady" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 13)
  - Theatrical productions: "Once Upon a Mattress" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
  - Theatrical productions: "South Pacific" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 15)
  - Theatrical productions: "Stalag 17" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 16)
  - Theatrical productions: "The Survivors" (Offsite-box 97, Folder 17)
  - Theatrical productions: "Tom Sawyer", 1970 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 18)
  - Theatrical productions: "Treasure Island", 1979 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 19)
  - Theatrical productions: Assorted productions, "A-L" (Offsite-box 98, Folder 1)
  - Theatrical productions: Assorted productions, "M-Z" (includes minstrel show) (Offsite-box 98, Folder 2)
  - Theatrical productions: unidentified (photo album) (Offsite-box 98, Folder 2-3)
  - Theatrical productions: unidentified (Offsite-box 98, Folder 4-6)
  - Theatrical productions: unidentified (Offsite-box 99, Folder 1-3)
  - Theatrical productions: unidentified (color) (Offsite-box 99, Folder 4)
  - Theatrical productions: cast portraits (Offsite-box 99, Folder 5)
  - Theatrical productions: Theater Committee meetings (Offsite-box 99, Folder 6)
  - Portraits: Boys (Offsite-box 100, Folder 1-5)
  - Portraits: Boys with Group Leaders (Offsite-box 100, Folder 6)
  - Portraits: Boys and Staff (Offsite-box 100, Folder 7)
  - Portraits: Groups (Offsite-box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - People receiving awards (Offsite-box 101, Folder 4)
  - Celebrities (Offsite-box 101, Folder 5-6)
    Includes photos of Mohammed Ali, Robert Moses, Floyd Patterson, Prince Rainier and Grace Kelly, Eleanor Roosevelt, Babe Ruth, Elizabeth Taylor, Cyrus Vance, and other notable figures.
  - Presidents and staff (Offsite-box 102, Folder 1)
  - Peter Capra (Offsite-box 102, Folder 2)